plrarticlesdownload.com 2012-06-08

# PlrArticlesDownload.Com - Privacy Policy

[Privacy Policy]

Your privacy is very important to us. I want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and I want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. 

I have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate my commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how I collect information from all end users of my Internet services (the "Services")-those who access some of my Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members")-what I do with the information I collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. I request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Personal Information I Collect and How It Is Used**

Introduction. I collect information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of my Services and the network of Web sites accessible through my Service. I use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use my Products and Services, and generally, **do not share this information with third parties.** However, I may disclose personal information collected if I have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when I believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below. 

Registration:  Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for my Products or Services including name, address, billing information. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. 

However, in instances where I and a partner jointly promote my Services, I may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. 

In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. I may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, I may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services. 

I, Partners and Sponsors:  Some products and services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature. 

Additionally, my partners may have advertisements or co-branded Web Pages that are cosponsored by an affiliate, independent contractor seller, or non-affiliated partner. I may share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered. 

Online Shopping:  At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. 

If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone number. I have no control over the third parties' use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so. 

If you order services or products directly from me I will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. I do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

Online Advertisements:  I may display my online advertisements. In those cases I share aggregated and non-identifying information about my Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. 

Additionally, in some instances, I use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company tells me the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information I have collected, I may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. I do not share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers or joint venture companies.

Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to me, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry I receive. I do not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

Voluntary Customer Surveys:  I may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. I encourage my customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services I offer and how I provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in my customer surveys is voluntary. 

I may take the information I receive from individuals responding to my Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers I may have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). I then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of my services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

Special Cases:  It is my policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors of Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

However, I may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through my Services, for any reason if, in my sole discretion, I believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating my Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect me and my Members. 

"Cookies" and How I Use Them. A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. I may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services I provide and to manage my telecommunications networks. 

If you are a Visitor or Member I may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. I do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

My Commitment to Children's Privacy. Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is my policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore I restrict my Web site to persons eighteen years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO. 

Public Forums:  Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of my Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. 

Mine Commitment to Data Security:  Services and Web sites I sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under my control. While I make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of my network and systems, I cannot guarantee that my security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

Where to Direct Questions About my Privacy Policy:  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web site. 

Revisions to This Policy: I reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, Terms Of Service agreement, and my other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting. 

Claim Your FREE Lifetime VIP Membership NOW 

And I'll Also Give You These Exclusive, 

UNIQUE PLR Products For FREE!

Simply, Enter Your Best Email to Download Your FREE Products!

**  
******  
**Best Email:**   

_IMPORTANT:_ ******Download will be sent to your email.** **Enter your correct email.  **Your details are protected and safe. It will never be sold!   

**What Does Private Label Rights Mean?**   
When you get **private label rights (AKA PLR, and private label resell rights)** to a product, it means that not only do you get the right to resell the product to your customers and keep 100% of the profits, you ALSO get the right to modify the product and usually you're allowed to put your name as the author/creator of the product. 

### Simply, Enter Your Best Email Above to Download Your FREE Products!

**© 2010 PlrArticlesDownload.com - All Rights Reserved.**
